# Juan Azula

I'm a young and passionate developer who has three years of programming experience. I excel in both frontend and backend development, I possess a broad mastery of various technologies and agile methodologies, supported by my focus on code quality and thorough testing implementation. I am willing to relocate for the right opportunity. **Committed to Ongoing Professional Growth.** 

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Manfacter, Castro-Urdiales(Hybrid): Lead Full Stack Developer

Mai 2024 - Current

As the Lead Developer, I assumed the ultimate responsibility for project development, successfully delivering a software application within the deadline that calculates the volume and price of 3D models uploaded by users depending on the selected production options. This application is full stack and includes a 3D model viewer and an AI assistant utilizing OpenAI's API.

# **Assembler Institute Of Technology,** Barcelona(remote): *Team Lead Software Developer*

Oct 2023 - June 2024

Instrumental in crafting robust, scalable software solutions with expertise spanning frontend and backend development, utilizing technologies like React, Next.js, Jest, Tailwind, TypeScript, and ORM tools. Championed best practices, including Agile, SOLID, and TDD within SCRUM, while spearheading the adoption of new technologies and mentoring team members.

# **Overstand Intelligence**, Barcelona(remote): *Machine Learning Developer*

Dec 2023 - Apr 2024

Innovative application of machine learning to optimize diverse use cases, employing advanced algorithms for data insights and business process optimization. Proactively explore advanced concepts for project facilitation, including computer vision applications like Lego piece detection.

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- o Advanced JavaScript and React in Ipartek Digital Innovation
- Angular in Ipartek Digital Innovation
- Java Development in Ipartek Digital Innovation
- o Html, Css, and JavaScript in
- o Ipartek Digital Innovation
- Big Data: Data Analysis and Visualization in Ipartek Digital Innovation
- Business Intelligence: Power Pivot and Power Bl in Ipartek Digital Innovation
- o Goethe Zertifikat B2 in German
- Frontend Development
  Certificate in Assembler Institute
- Backend Development Certificate in Assembler Institute
- Advanced Development Certificate in Assembler Institute

# San Sebastián, Spain (34) 626 422 524

juanazula3@gmail.com github linkedin portfolio

#### **SKILLS**

- Python and Node Backend Frameworks (Django, Flask, Express, Nest)
- JS Frontend Frameworks (React, Vue, Angular, Svelte)
- E2E, Unit and Integration Testing (Playwright, Cypress, Jest, Vitest, Pytest, RTL)
- Programming Languages
  (JavaScript, Python, TypeScript, PHP, Java)
- SQL and NO-SQL Databases (PostgreSQL, SQLite, MySQL, MongoDB, Redis)
- $\cdot$  CI/CD with github actions and jenkins
- Knowledge of authentication, AWS, Azure, Docker, deployment and git
- ·Scrum/Agile

# **EDUCATION**

- Master of Software Development in AIT (2023-24)
- Bachelor, Software Systems Science in Otto-Friedrich Universität Bamberg (Two Semesters 2022-23)
- Python Programing in Tokio School (2021-22)
- · Abitur in Naturwissenschaften in Deutsche Schule San Sebastián(2021)

### REFERENCES

José Valenzuela: Tech Lead & Software Developer at Assembler Institute of Technology +34637550127 Jose linkedin

Víctor Jauregui: CEO & Founder at Alonbalon +34697500090 <u>Víctor linkedin</u>

## **LANGUAGES**

Spanish(Native), German(B2), English(B2), Basque(B2), Mongol.